<resources>
    // App name and top bar name
    <string name="app_name">Health Studio</string>
    <string name="fitness_page">Fitness Studio</string>
    <string name="account_page">Your Account</string>

    // Top bar greetings
    <string name="morning">Good Morning!</string>
    <string name="afternoon">Good Afternoon!</string>
    <string name="night">Good Evening!</string>

    // Button's text
    <string name="get_info">Get More Info</string>
    <string name="unlock_more_function">Unlock More Function</string>
    <string name="import_button">Import</string>

    // Import page title
    <string name="import_title">Import Your Information</string>
    <string name="import_text_field_title">Choice your information type here</string>
    <string name="import_value_title">Input the value here</string>
    <string name="enter_value">Enter Value</string>

    // Data exception alert
    <string name="h_heart_rate">！！Heart rate is currently high, so it is recommended to pay
        attention to rest and relaxation！！</string>
    <string name="l_heart_rate">！！Heart rate is low, may be fatigue or low blood pressure, please
        pay attention to health condition!！</string>
    <string name="l_walk_distance">The number of steps today is low, it is recommended to move
        more to stay active!</string>
    <string name="l_sleep_time">You are a short sleeper, so it is recommended to sleep at least
        6 hours a day.</string>
    <string name="h_activity">Excessive calorie consumption may indicate a slowdown in the renewal
        process, which might lead to obesity.</string>
    <string name="l_activity">Excessive calorie consumption can lead to energy deficiency and
        weakened immunity.</string>
    <string name="h_fitness">The excessive calorie consumption caused by intense workouts can
        undermine the health. Therefore, we suggest that one should not exceed three hours of
        exercise per day.</string>
    <string name="l_fitness">If the calories burned during fitness activities are too low, it may
        lead to poor results.</string>
    <string name="h_stand">Excessive standing time can lead to lumbar muscle strain.</string>
    <string name="l_stand">Excessive short standing periods can lead to problems with muscles and
        bones.</string>

    // The documents in app
    <string name="health_intro">In the fast pace of modern life, it is vital to maintain physical
        health, health not only means the absence of disease, but also includes good physical
        fitness, mental state and lifestyle, and through scientific management of health data and
        regular recording of health indicators (such as heart rate steps) Sleep time, etc.), we can
        better understand their physical condition, adjust life habits in time, improve the quality
        of life, and find small changes in the body, take early measures, such as long-term lack of
        sleep may affect the immune system, and irregular heart rate may be a signal of potential
        health problems</string>
    <string name="fitness_intro">Fitness can not only build muscle strength, improve heart and lung
        function and promote new circulation, but also effectively relieve stress, improve sleep
        quality, and enhance overall health. By scientifically recording exercise data (such as
        step count, heart rate, calorie consumption, etc.), we can more intuitively understand our
        own exercise, adjust training programs, improve exercise efficiency, while avoiding sports
        injuries, and maintain long-term health and vitality.</string>
    <string name="import_health_title">Import your health data, and let us do the hard work of
        tracking and evaluating it for you. </string>
    <string name="import_health_data">Whether you re looking to improve your overall health
        or simply stay on top of your wellness. We’ll provide insightful analysis, giving you the
        tools you need to make informed decisions and live your healthiest life.</string>
    <string name="import_fitness_title">Sync your fitness data effortlessly and take your workout
        tracking to the next level. </string>
    <string name="import_fitness_data">Our app helps you track calories burned, fitness minutes,
        active hours, and more offering personalized insights tailored to your fitness goals.
        Whether you re training for a marathon or just staying fit, we ll support you every step
        of the way, helping you assess progress and achieve your fitness aspirations with
        ease.</string>
    <string name="intro_title">The Introduction of Health Studio</string>
    <string name="intro_text">Health Studio is a comprehensive record app that records various
        data of your body and fitness. It helps you keep track of them by having users manually
        input your physical health data. Thus, you do not need to download multiple apps to view
        your various physical health data and fitness records! The mission of Health Studio is to
        make your life more convenient!</string>
    <string name="howto_title">Instructions of How to Use</string>
    <string name="howto_text">Welcome! New user, I know you must be confused about how to use my
        software. Here is an introduction to the App: On the Health page, your inputted health
        indicators will be displayed. On the Fitness page, your inputted fitness records will be
        shown. How to input the indicators or records? Just click on the indicator or record card
        on the Health or Fitness page to start entering your data!</string>

    // Documents for membership popup
    <string name="member_title">Get Health+ and Fitness+ Now!</string>
    <string name="member_text">Unlock Your Best Self with Health+ and Fitness+! Why settle for
        average? When you can achieve more? With Health+ and Fitness+, you’ll unlock premium
        features designed to help you track! Health+ Features: Sleep Tracking – Improve your rest
        quality. Hearing Monitoring – Protect your ears from loud noise. Resting Heart Rate –
        Understand your heart trends. Annual Health Report – Get a full-year health summary.
        Fitness+ Perks: Personalized Fitness Advice – Get workouts tailored to you! Upgrade now
        for a healthier, stronger you!</string>
    <string name="to_be_continue">Coming Soon…</string>
</resources>