<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HealthStudio</string>
    <string name="get_info">Get More Info</string>
    <string name="unlock_more_function">Unlock More Function</string>
    <string name="import_button">Import</string>
    <string name="go_to_setting">Go To Setting</string>
    <string name="import_health_data">Import your health data, and let us do the hard work of
        tracking and evaluating it for you. Whether you re looking to improve your overall health
        or simply stay on top of your wellness. We’ll provide insightful analysis, giving you the
        tools you need to make informed decisions and live your healthiest life.</string>
    <string name="import_fitness_data">Sync your fitness data effortlessly and take your workout
        tracking to the next level. Our app helps you track calories burned, fitness minutes,
        active hours, and more offering personalized insights tailored to your fitness goals.
        Whether you re training for a marathon or just staying fit, we ll support you every step
        of the way, helping you assess progress and achieve your fitness aspirations with
        ease.</string>
    <string name="intro_title">The Introduction of Health Studio</string>
    <string name="intro_text">Health Studio is a comprehensive record app that records various
        data of your body and fitness. It helps you keep track of them by having users manually
        input your physical health data. Thus, you do not need to download multiple apps to view
        your various physical health data and fitness records! The mission of Health Studio is to
        make your life more convenient!</string>
    <string name="howto_title">Instructions of How to Use</string>
    <string name="howto_text">Welcome! New user, I know you must be confused about how to use my
        software. Here is an introduction to the App: On the Health page, your inputted health
        indicators will be displayed. On the Fitness page, your inputted fitness records will be
        shown. How to input the indicators or records? Just click on the indicator or record card
        on the Health or Fitness page to start entering your data!</string>
</resources>